babyshowerstuff.com 2010-03-08

# Baby Shower Stuff

_This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information about your shopping experience. Please see the[Yahoo! Privacy Policy](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/) for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information._

 **Privacy Statement for Big Dot of Happiness, LLC  
(BabyShowerStuff.com is owned and operated by BigDotofHappiness.com)**

**Our Commitment To Privacy:**  
We at Big Dot of Happiness are fanatics about everything, including your privacy. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

 **The Information We Collect:**  
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on BigDotOfHappiness.com. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: Name Address Email address Phone number Credit/Debit Card Information (etc.)

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are: Name Address Phone Number (etc.)

 **The Way We Use Information:**  
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order to fulfill, bill and ship your order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

We use email addresses provided to communicate your order status. Once your order has been placed you will receive a confirmation email to let you know your order is being processed. You will also receive a confirmation email once your order has been shipped. An email will be sent if a problem arises with your order. We use return email addresses to answer emails that we receive.

We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to fulfill and ship the product. We offer gift cards and text options by which you can personalize a product you order for another person. Information you provide to us to create a gift card or text for personalization is only used for that purpose, and is only shared with the person receiving the gift or product. You can make requests and register to receive materials or information. Information you submit on our website will only be used for this purpose and not shared with outside parties.

Finally, we **NEVER** use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

 **Other Ways We Use Information:**  
Cookies are small text files that can be created and stored on your computer. Cookies are used to collect non-identifying information. This information is used to compile how many visits were made to the website, what pages were looked at, and for use in the ordering process. This non-identifying information is used to make the site more user friendly and to measure site traffic. You may choose how your browser handles cookies.

 **Our Commitment To Data Security:**  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

 **Children’s Privacy:**  
This website is not intended for children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect information on children under that age.

 **How To Contact Us:**  
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 800-274-4282, send us an email at [smiles@bigdotofhappiness.com](mailto:smiles@bigdotofhappiness.com), or contact:  
Big Dot of Happiness  
412 Technology Drive East  
Menomonie, WI 54751
